我想被连接啊
英文字幕: Horriblesubs
中文字幕: 布尔
本字幕参照英文字幕制作
可能会由于
1. 日译英的瑕疵
2. 英译汉的瑕疵
而产生偏差
请根据自己情况使用
或者等待更精确的版本
Use it at your own risk
Nii-san gave up everything for me.
哥哥为我放弃了一切
So I'm going to give up what's most precious to me, too.
所以我也要放弃对我而言最宝贵的东西
Why are you throwing it away?
为什么你要把它扔掉
Do you hate it now?
你讨厌它吗
No.
不
But to survive, I have to throw it away.
但为了生存下去 我必须得扔掉它
Was that the same for me, too?
对我而言也是如此吗
I'm not connected to anyone.
我没和任何人相连
People realize they were connected when they no longer are.
只有在失去联系时人们才会察觉到联系的存在
I have to protect the connections I have.
我必须保护我拥有的联系
So I'm giving up soccer.
所以我要放弃足球
Take it.
拿着它
Some dreams come true because you're disconnected.
有时候切断某些联系才能让你梦想成真
Of course he wouldn't remember.
他肯定早忘了
I guess this is the last time I see this place.
我觉得这是我看这里的最后一眼了
Nii-san.
哥哥
Is everything okay?
没事儿吧
What's going on?
怎么样了
Who knows?
谁知道
But there's a good chance they've sniffed out what happened four years ago.
不过他们很可能得知了四年前的事情
You'd better not still be thinking that it's your fault.
你别老自责 那事儿并不是你的错
Not really.
没有
Don't forget, though.
当然也别忘了
Just as you need me, I need you.
正如你需要我一样 我也需要你
Come with me, Toi.
悠 跟我来吧
Nii-san...
哥哥
What's wrong?
怎么了
Give me just a little time.
给我点儿时间
No, I'm going with you.
我还是要跟你走
I've made up my mind about that.
我已经做好决定了
But there are a couple of people I want to make sure are okay.
我只是想看看几个人 确保他们没事儿
I haven't seen you make that face in a while.
我好久没看到你这样的表情了
Fine, fine.
没事儿
I'll be waiting.
我会等着的
But only for one day.
但只等一天
Yeah.
好
Once the background blends together,there's an invisible street corner
There we are, crying out with fading voices
Go forth with the tearing pain
As though you'd just crawledaway from the worst night ever
You're always alone
Your heart is shouting a sound of desire
If we can ever talk again,if we can ever connect
I'd be overwhelmed
You grow more and more distant
I chase after you
To tell you my brand new feelings for you
I run like mad
Present, past and future
I want to be connected with you
By our feelings, by the depths of our souls
Damn it, Kazuki! That bastard!
可恶 一稀那个混蛋
Why do I have to take all the flack?
为啥得要我来泄漏啊
Who's more important, me or him?
是我还是他重要
Huh?
啊
Out of balls already?
已经没球了吗
Damn it, everything sucks.
该死 简直糟透了
When everything sucks, just throw it all away.
如果事情都糟透了 把他们抛掉就好了
You only live once.
人生只有一次
You don't get extra lives.
可没有多余的生命给你
Holy...
真的……
See?
瞧
Is there something on my face?
我脸上有什么东西吗
No, nothing.
没啥
Oh, here. Thanks.
给你这个 谢谢你
Helping people sure does pay off.
帮助他人总有回报
Tch.
切
The leader of a fraud ring that was working out of the Tama region...
在多摩地区实施欺诈的团体的头目离开了那里
Why do we have to deal with it?
为什么非得我们来做
The suspect lives in this town.
嫌疑人在这片街道里
So?
所以呢
2019年4月到6月间发生的东京多摩地区的欺诈案件
Apparently, he's wanted in connection to a fatal shooting four years ago.
很明显 他因为和四年前的枪击谋杀案有联系而被通缉
If we capture him, we can easily make him a kappa zombie.
如果我们抓住了他 就能轻而易举地将他变成河童僵尸
Look at this half-baked doll, so eager to please those people.
看看这个半生不熟的人偶先生 热切地希望讨好他人
Do you honestly think this'll change my mind?
你真认为这能说服我吗
This is only half-baked.
这玩意儿还没烤透啊
A-All clear.
这边安全
行人优先
Man, I owe you.
这算我欠你的
Do you know this place well?
你对这儿很熟吗
I used to hang out here with Kazu—my friend—ever since I was little.
我小时候常和一……我朋友来这儿玩
Everything changes before you know it.
世事无常
The town, the people...
此地此人
尽情跳舞歌唱吧
Did you do something bad?
你做了什么坏事儿吗
Hey, Specs, how old are you?
眼镜仔 你多大了
Huh?
呃
I'm fourteen. Why?
我14岁 问这干嘛
You're pretty small for fourteen.
你看上去比14岁小啊
Sarafuku
日本黄瓜
Sarafuku黄瓜
That's none of your business!
这跟你没关系
My bad.
我的锅
I happen to have a brother that's about your age.
我恰好有个弟弟和你差不多大
I know.
我知道
I don't know if it's because I haven't kept up with him for a while,
我不知道是不是因为我好久没陪他
but he's gotten so grown-up. He's not cute anymore.
他现在变得很成熟了 不再那么可爱了
I'm leaving town with him.
我要带他离开这片街道
I can't let myself get caught right now.
我现在不能被抓
Hey...
嘿
If it's all right with you, I'd like to help.
如果和你在一块儿不碍事 我愿意帮你
Huh?
呃
联盟
Grow up already.
大人不生小孩气儿
But aren't you pissed off, too?
你难道不生气吗
We could have granted your wish by now.
本来现在就可以给你许愿的
I'm disappointed in Enta.
我对燕太很失望
He lied to us and betrayed us.
他欺骗 背叛了我们
I'm sure he has his reasons.
我相信他做这些是有原因的
What reasons?
什么原因
Well...
呃……
That's not for me to say.
这不该我来说
What the hell?
什么鬼
So you two are keeping a secret?
所以你俩之间还有什么秘密
Why are you siding with Enta?
你为啥支持燕太
No, that's not what I'm doing.
我不是我没有
Forget it.
算了
I'm going to find the dishes.
我这就去找盘子
Hey!
嘿
河童广场
Shit. I'm not good at handling these situations...
可恶 我不擅长处理这种状况……
Shikotama的老大 在躲藏？
我有重要的事情今天得告诉王子dish 我从未想过他们 是幕后黑手dish……但是对我而言他们不像坏人
Now for the next story, dish.
现在是下一条新闻
The police force has made an emergency deployment
警察正在开展紧急行动
in response to the possibility that Kuji Chikai, 25,
来应对25岁久慈誓的事件
wanted leader of nefarious fraud ring Shikotama, is hiding out in Asakusa.
他是邪恶犯罪团伙Shikotama的头目 正在浅草地区隐匿
Freeze! Freeze!
不许动 不许动
I'm out of time.
我没时间了
花屋敷
I haven't been to Hanayashiki in ages.
我好多年没去过花屋敷了
He used to follow me around,all like, "Nii-chan, Nii-chan..."
他以前老是围着我转 叫我 哥哥 哥哥 的
Before I knew it, he's a different person.
他和现在可不一样
He's trying to choose between me and his buddies right now.
现在他在我和他的朋友之间做出选择
Buddies?
朋友
I mean, I can't blame him.
我的意思是 我当然不能怪他
I made him give up something precious to him, after all.
毕竟我已经让他放弃了他认为宝贵的东西
That's the end of it.
这就完了
Forget about the gun.
忘了那把手枪
Got it?
知道吗
Yeah.
好
I'll catch up with you later.
我待会找你 哥哥
You gave up everything for me.
哥哥 你为我付出了一切
So I'm going to give up what's most precious to me, too.
所以我也要放弃对我而言最宝贵的东西
He gave up soccer.
他放弃了足球
He used to say he wanted to become a soccer player when he grew up.
他曾说他长大后想要成为足球运动员
No...
不……
...way...
……会吧……
This miçanga...
这个友谊链……
He said he gave the miçanga away, too.
他说他会把这个友谊链也送出去
To who?!
送给谁啊
Who did he give it to?!
他送给了谁啊
I wouldn't know.
我不知道
I'm sure he wanted someone to remember how much soccer meant to him.
我相信他会把这个友谊链送给能记住他有多么喜欢足球的人
He's too earnest, really.
他是认真的
He'd put himself in danger or get his hands dirty for my sake.
他是那种为了我 会赴汤蹈火的人
Even though it's not like I asked him to.
就算我没让他这么去做
Me, too.
我 也是
I would have done anything for Kazuki.
我会为一稀付出一切
No matter how much you do for someone, if it bears no fruit, it's not worth anything.
不管你为别人付出了多少 只要没有成果 也就没有意义
That depends on how you look at it yourself.
这取决于你怎么看待这个成果的分量
Just do whatever will make things easiest for you, then.
当然啦 最简单的方式就是做任何你觉得能做的事情
过山车
That's...
这……
I guess I'm out of time.
我觉得没时间了
You are.
你说的没错
Hurry up, take your brother, and leave.
快点儿带着你弟弟离开吧
Chikai...
誓……
Who the heck is that?
他是谁
Oh, shit.
呃 该死
I'm going to avenge my bro!
我要为我大哥复仇
No, I, uh...
不 我 呃……
H-Hey!
嘿 等等
Yo, kid.
哟 小孩
Are you with Chikai?
你和誓是一伙儿的吗
N-No, I'm not.
我不是我没有
Don't play dumb with me!
别给我装傻
Over here, policeman!
警察在这儿哦
We're the police.
我们 是警察
This happens all the time.
这种事儿太常见了
What are you doing to that child?
你要对这个小孩儿做啥
You're violating the Firearms and Swords Control Act, you know.
你违反了武器控制法哦
I've lived my life until now to kill Chikai.
我要活到杀死誓的那一天
Shit, shit, shit!
不好不好不好
Chikai...
誓……
Are you talking about the wanted fugitive, Kuji Chikai?
你在说被通缉的那个逃犯久慈誓吗
I'm not letting you popos have him!
我不会让你们这些条子抓住他的
Let him take responsibility for taking out my bro!
让他为杀死我大哥这事儿付出代价
This guy's so stuffy.
这人脑子太一根筋了
Kuji's gotten away already.
久慈都跑了
Quit babbling!
别在那儿唠唠叨叨的
Damn it...
该死
Stay out of our way.
别妨碍我们的事儿
We're in the middle of the street, but oh well.
虽然是我们在路中间 但是啊
Do you think you can threaten me with that?
你觉得那玩意儿能威胁到我吗
We'll open this door for you.
来打开一扇门吧
Desire or love?
是欲望还是爱
What do we do with this?
接下来怎么处理
He's valuable kappa zombie material.
他可是宝贵的河童僵尸素材
What was that gunshot?
刚刚那声枪响怎么回事
There's a man down.
有个人倒地了
Oh dear, we got caught.
天哪 我们被发现了
He's dead.
他死了
Did you two shoot him?
是你俩开的枪吗
This isn't going to pass as self-defense.
这可不能被当作正当防卫处理了
Hey, why don't you two say something?
嘿 你俩说点啥啊
It was Kuji the fugitive who shot him.
是久慈那个在逃犯杀的他
What are you talking about?
你在说啥
Kuji made enemies from the incident four years ago.
久慈四年前树下了很多敌人
Exactly.
没错
It's Kuji's fault.
这是久慈的锅
But there's no proof of that anywhere...
但是这没有证据能证明这件事……
Who shot this man?
谁开枪打死他的
Kuji the fugitive.
久慈那个逃犯
Without a doubt.
毫无疑问
I've been watching them for the past few days.
我这几天都在观察他们
I'm certain that these two people have captured Dark Keppi-sama, dish.
我确信他俩抓住了黑暗河童王子 dish
水獭歌酱炒面
Reo and Mabu...
玲央和真武……
I never thought they'd still be alive, kero.
不敢相信他们还活着 呱呱
And this is our secret anti-otter weapon, dish!
这个是我们的秘密反獭武器 dish
反獭秘密武器
What's this?
这是什么
It freezes the target solid at the flick of a switch, so we can catch them alive, dish.
他能在按下开关后迅速冰冻目标 这样我们就能活捉他们 dish
I see.
这样啊
Then let's first determine their current location, kero.
首先确定一下他们的位置 呱呱
河童轩
Sara胡椒粉
Can't fight on an empty stomach.
不能饿着开打
Pepper...
胡椒……
Prince!
王子
Out cold...
冻晕了……
Oh no, dish!
哦不 dish
The live broadcast is coming up, dish.
直播马上就要开始了 dish
I can't be late!
我不能迟到
You're so horrible!
你也太过分了
I thought I was dead!
我以为我已经死了
The bad ones are the ones who survive in this world.
这个世界只有坏人才能生存下去
Softies like you should be careful, Specs.
像你这样的心肠软的人应该要小心 眼镜仔
You think you have the right to say that?
你觉得你 有权这么说我吗
Well, now that you're still alive, you should go make up with your buddies.
既然你现在活着 你应该去和你的朋友和好才是
No, I don't really...
不 我真的……
I gotta go.
我得走了
Share those with your buddies.
和朋友们一起吃吧
Hey, Masa.
嘿 雅
I'm taking a boat there now.
我要坐船走了
Toi's coming, too, of course.
悠当然也来
Jinnai?
阵内
About Yasaka...
关于矢逆的事情……
Why didn't you say anything?
为啥你要瞒着啊
Huh?
呃
About the miçanga you gave Kazuki!
友谊链是你送给一稀的事情
He remembered?
他想起来了吗
No, I don't think he realizes.
不 他应该没想起来
I see.
好吧
Of course.
当然了
Why didn't you tell Kazuki?
为啥你没跟一稀说啊
He doesn't remember anything.
他记不起来的
There's no reason to tell him now.
而且现在也没理由告诉他
You two go on as the golden duo.
你俩可以继续当黄金搭档
Are you happy with that?
你这样就开心吗
I'm going to live for my brother.
我要为我哥哥而活了
Bye.
再见
You're such a bad liar.
你这个大骗子
Not here, either.
这儿也没有
This was where I first met him, wasn't it?
这不就是我和他初次见面的地方吗
I used to think Toi was scary and bad news.
当时我还以为悠是可怕的
Hello?
喂
Toi?
悠
I don't need the dishes anymore.
我不需要那些盘子了
I'm leaving town.
我要离开这里了
Wh-What are you talking about?
你——你在说啥
Are you angry about what happened?
你对这事儿很生气吗
What's wrong?
怎么了
Say something!
说话啊
Hang on.
等等
I'll do something about it.
我会想办法解决问题的
Please don't leave, Toi!
别走啊 悠
People realize they were connected when they no longer are.
只有在失去联系时人们才会察觉到联系的存在
What?
什么
What are you talking about?
你在说啥
I have to protect the connections I have left.
我得保护我剩下的联系
Toi!
悠
Toi...
悠……
Did I make you give up something precious again?
你又因为我放弃了什么宝贵的东西了吗
Not really.
也没有
They aren't like that.
他们并不宝贵
河童广场
There you are.
到了
Kazuki!
一稀
We have to hurry. Toi's leaving.
我们得快点儿 悠正准备走
He's really...
他真的……
It's your fault.
这是你的错
It's your fault that Toi's leaving.
是你让悠离开的
Toi could have stayed with us if we had the dishes.
如果我们有盘子 悠应该和我们在一起的
I feel bad for Toi.
悠真的可怜
What the hell...
这算什么啊
You keep saying, "Toi, Toi," but you're the worst for forgetting something so precious.
你老是说着 悠 悠 的 但遗忘了最重要的事情的你才是最差的吧
You should have realized what he was trying to do!
你应该理解他要做的事情啊
Why would I listen to anything you have to say?
我为啥要听燕太你说的
You betrayed us.
你背叛了我们
I'm done...
燕太……
with you.
我要和你绝交
Yeah, well, I...
可我……
I...
我……
Found you.
找到你了
Cops?
警察
There they are.
他们在这儿
The Dishes of Hope.
希望之皿
Why...
什么
Why do we know about the dishes, you ask?
你要问 我们是怎么知道这些盘子的
You don't need to know.
你没必要知道
Now, it's time to open the door.
到开门时间了
Desire or love?
欲望还是爱
Kazuki!
一稀
Enta!
燕太
Do you want to save your friend's life?
你想救你朋友一命吗
Well, too bad!
很可惜
The Dishes of Hope are going to grant our wishes.
希望之皿将会实现我们 的愿望
That's enough.
这可以了
Let's go.
我们走吧
Come on, it was just getting good.
干嘛扫兴啊
Call for help.
求救吧
He might still have time.
他可能还来得及
Kazuki...
一稀……
Enta! Are you all right?
燕太 你还好吗
Why would you do this?
你为啥这么做
It's no use.
不行
I couldn't even say it as a joke...
就算只是开玩笑……
That I hate you.
我也说不出我讨厌你
No...
不……
Enta...
燕太……
Enta!
燕太
想
要
相
连
可
是
却
又
不
能
见
面
Stand by me
Please
I don't know if I can become stronger
The rain washes away my tears
I want to be embraced by your warmth
The flickering lightbulb that's been neglected
One morning, it had quietly died
It's almost like you and me
Like the fleeting moment whenwe held our hands together
I sat with my arms around my knees
Thinking of the days long gone
Stand by me
Please
I don't know if I can become stronger
Even if you aren't here now
Please give me the courage to reach out
Stand by you
Please
I want to get rid of everything
The rain washes away my tears
I just want to be embraced by your warmth
Urgent, urgent.
紧急 紧急
Emergency orders from headquarters.
总部发来的紧急命令
Shots fired in the jurisdiction of Asazara Police Station. Shots fired.
在浅草警局的辖区内发生了枪击事件 枪击事件
All units in area to the site.
邻近各单位注意
Asazara 3 to headquarters.
浅草3号报告总部
本故事纯属虚构。
所有登场人物及团体均与现实无关。